http://www.foodallergy.com/privacy-policy/

Main MenuHomeAbout Alletess BackAbout AlletessOur ServicesAllergy & Immunology BackAllergy & ImmunologyInhalant AllergensFood AllergiesYeast and Mold AllergiesGut ImmunityTest Menu BackTest MenuAvailable TestsOrder a Test KitSerum Instructional VideoFinger Stick Instructional VideoFor CliniciansNutrition & Wellness BackNutrition & WellnessNutrition SupportWellness PlansResource Center BackResource CenterWebsites & AppsFrequently Asked QuestionsContact Us About AlletessAbout Alletess MedicalOur ServicesAllergy & ImmunologyInhalant AllergensFood AllergiesYeast and MoldsGut ImmunityTest MenuAvailable TestsSerum Instructional VideoFinger Stick Instructional VideoOrder a Test KitFor CliniciansClinician LoginShareFile ResultsNutrition & WellnessNutrition SupportWellness PlansResource CenterWebsites & AppsFrequently Asked Questions For CliniciansHomeContact UsPrivacy PolicyAt Alletess, Inc. (“Alletess Medical Laboratory”), we are dedicated to protecting your privacy and safeguarding your personally identifiable information. We have provided this Privacy Statement as an explanation of the information we collect, how we use it, how the use of this information can benefit your experience on our web site. We also describe the measures we take to protect the security of the information and how you can contact us about our privacy practices. Our privacy practices may vary among the countries in which we operate to reflect local practices and legal requirements. We wish to help you make informed decisions, so please take a moment to read the sections below.PURPOSE FOR COLLECTION, PROCESSING, AND DISCLOSURE:Collection & UseWithin the Alletess Medical Laboratory web site, you can order products or services, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are name, contact and billing information (including shipping address and end-user), transaction, and credit card information.Alletess, Inc. is fully committed to providing you with information about the collection and use of PHI furnished by, or collected from, visitors while using our web site, products and services. It is our practice providing services such as processing a transaction (e.g., completing a test kit order or fulfilling a request for information). Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing and are not retained for other purposes.Marketing and communications with you in relation to the products and laboratory services offered by Alletess, Inc.Alletess, Inc. will not use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the uses described above. Alletess, Inc. will make every effort to apply local country laws and policies where they differ from those in the U.S., if any.SECURITY SAFEGUARDS:Alletess, Inc. recognizes the importance of information security, and is constantly reviewing and enhancing our technical, physical, and logical security rules and procedures. Our web site and servers have security measures in place to help protect your PII against accidental, loss, misuse, unlawful or unauthorized access, disclosure, or alteration while under our control. Although “guaranteed security” does not exist either on or off the Internet, we safeguard your information using appropriate administrative, procedural and technical safeguards, including password controls, “firewalls” and the use of up to 256-bit encryption based on a Class 3 Digital Certificate issued by Earthlink, Inc.  This allows for the use of Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an encryption method used to help protect your data from interception and hacking while in transit. Available TestsAlletess Medical Laboratory conducts comprehensive and thorough allergy & immunology testing worldwide.
Order a Test KitNow you can order a test kit online. Follow the simple guidelines and we will ship the kit directly to you.
Clinician LoginOrder test kits for your office, download test forms to order your patients' lab tests, see a schedule of fees, and access other valuable resources.
